//holds data for questions

const STORE = [
    {
        question: '1. What are the four right hand fingers, in order from thumb to ring, called?',
        answers: [
            'p-m-a-i',
            't-i-m-r',
            'p-i-m-a',
            '1-2-3-4'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'p-i-m-a'
    },
    {
       question: '2. Who is considered the most important person in the development of classical guitar literature and performance in the 20th century?',
       answers: [
            'Andres Segovia',
            'John Williams',
            'Jimi Hendrix',
            'Robert Johnson',
       ],
       correctAnswer: 'Andres Segovia'
    },
    {
        question: '3. The most famous concerto for classical guitar, Concierto de Aranjuez by Joaquin Rodrigo, was first performed in which year?',
        answers: [
             '1940',
             '1823',
             '1967',
             '1951',
        ],
        correctAnswer: '1940'

    }, 
    {
        question: '4. The technique used to play the strings rapidly with all four fingers in succession is called what?  Use "Recuerdos de la Alhambra" as an example.',
        answers: [
             'apoyando',
             'tremolo',
             'slurs',
             'glissando',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'tremolo'
    }, 
    {
        question: '5. Which of these famous composers actually wrote a piece for the classical guitar?',
        answers: [
             'Ludwig van Beethoven',
             'Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart',
             'Erik Satie',
             'Benjamin Britten',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Benjamin Britten'
    }, 
    {
        question: '6. Which luthier helped popularize a raised neck in the 1980s?',
        answers: [
             'Antonio Torres',
             'Thomas Humphrey',
             'Daniel Friedrich',
             'Jose Ramirez',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Daniel Friedrich'
    },
    {
        question: '7.  In which piece are the words, "Charlotte, adieu" written at the end of the piece?',
        answers: [
             'Fantaisie Elegiaque by Sor',
             'Fantasie Hongroise by Mertz',
             'Fantasia para un Gentilhombre by Rodrigo',
             'Elegy by Rawsthorne',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Fantaisie Elegiaque by Sor'

    }, 
    {
        question: '8. Which 20th century composer wrote for the Assad Brothers?',
        answers: [
             'Benjamin Britten',
             'Joan Tower',
             'Astor Piazzolla',
             'Toru Takemitsu',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Astor Piazzolla'

    }, 
    {
        question: '9. Which piece did Kazuhiro Yamashita famously transcribe?',
        answers: [
             'Pictures at an Exhibition by Mussorgsky',
             '9th Symphony by Beethoven',
             'Adagio for Strings by Barber',
             '5th Symphony by Dvorak',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Pictures at an Exhibition by Mussorgsky'

    }, 
    {
        question: '10. What is the tuning for Koyunbaba by Carlo Domeniconi?',
        answers: [
             'EADGBE',
             'DGDGBD',
             'C#G#C#G#C#E',
             'EbADG#BE',
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'C#G#C#G#C#E'

    }

]